[{"answer": "Well, we were on the road.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "And what happened next?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "So you could see possible life at the end of the tunnel, couldn't you?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yes, my wife still has problems with me.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Do you still have any cognitive problems?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Piers, there's no -- there's no proof, you know, scientifically or medically that having a family around you in moments like that step up your recovery.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "How important looking back do you think it is to have a spouse who's just absolutely there for you?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I've spoken to -- I've spoken to Mark, you know, her husband, who's been a remarkable astronaut, and I've covered that as well at NASA.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Have you been able to talk to any of Gabby Giffords' family throughout this process?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "You know, in some ways, Piers, I don't really -- I don't really know what to say.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "What do you -- what do you say to her?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "You know what, good and bad.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "You mean good news or bad news?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "You know, some people have actually said that.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Do you think you're a better reporter in a strange way for what you've been through?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Well, I -- when I was going up, I knew my body was back there, like I caught a glimpse of it.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Did you see yourself at all in any of this?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Mm-hmm.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Attached to it?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Like did you feel attached to it?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "You know, this is -- this is one of those things that we will know the absolute truth of what it is that we saw and what we lived through, you know, when we die.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Do you believe it was a religious thing or -- well, what was it?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Now is there a delay between the table?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "I said foxiest bikini model but you couldn't put that in the prompter.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "But is it true?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Do you seek outrage?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Because it's fun.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Do you have any filter?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "It's not obviously identifiable, I have to say.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Have you seen one?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "The Tea Party --", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "You mean the Tea Party?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "And cancelled.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Where's my light?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "No filter.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Filter?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Not with the Bachmanns.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Daughters?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "You're an American citizen.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "What can I not tell you?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Well, I think that when I perform on the road I always thank the audience for buying a ticket because it's a big deal to buy a ticket for a live entertainment, get a baby-sitter and pay for the meal, the parking, whatever.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "What do you think, in all seriousness, about what's happening to your country?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Do you think -- do you think Washington politicians have any real connect now to the American public?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Yes, he brought the stimulus package that clearly hasn't been working.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "How do you make a deal with people who don't want to make a deal?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "My views about politics?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "You are, you're a businesswoman.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Honey, if I -- well, how good is that?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Because I don't think --", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Why are you shy about being serious about the economy?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "I actually do a lot of political humor, I do more now probably than I ever have.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Why do you find it so absurd that I would ask you?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Because you know, these politicians, they have quotes, they're the gift that keeps on giving.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I think it'd be fun, it'd be newsworthy.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Would you want to do that?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "You want to get Anderson fired.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Which was?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Do you worry about being taken seriously?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I'm going to climb over the table.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "That's called a commercial bumper.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "What is happening here?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I have no issue with that.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Are we going to be de-robing as the show goes on?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Do you dream wistfully of being fired in totally (INAUDIBLE) and disgrace one day?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Becoming unemployable?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Well, I think because -- you know, when I started doing my show, reality was in a really different place.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Why if you love it so much is it not on air anymore?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Just try and control yourself.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Why can't -- why?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Well, the Twitter-sphere is going rather crazy about your performance so far.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "That's the best adjective you can come up with?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Steve Martin.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "All right, who else?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Is he as fun at a private dinner party as I would hope he is?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Did you -- did you give him a lap dance?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Bit of a brazen hussy, aren't you?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "First of all, like he knows who you are.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "What did Jack Nicholson think would be a terrible social network moment?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Doesn't he?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Not once.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Did he talk about me?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Hold on.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "Actually, they've luckily gone back since the trial ended.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "Do you watch HLN, because they're getting better numbers than you at this point?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Did you cover Casey Anthony?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "I think she's a force for good.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "Where are the twins?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Don't you think?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "Ninety one.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "How old is she now?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "And you're admitting it?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "I'm from Offuly (ph), is where my family eventually ended up.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "What town are you from?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "It's a place called Banahurn Offuly (ph), which is about an hour from Dublin.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Fact check, is there a fact check department?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "I do when I watch \"My Big Fat Gypsy Wedding.\"", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "Do you feel Irish?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "We can beat this because we're going to talk about your plastic surgery.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 766, "question": "How can we top this conversation?", "qSentId": 765}, {"answer": "I haven't had any.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "What about yours?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "Yes, please.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "You want to go down the list?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "Did it?", "qSentId": 793}, {"answer": "Probably -- this is so sick, but the first time I had it all done, I did like a trade out which is really one of my best whore moments ever.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 804, "question": "How much have you spent in total on resculpting?", "qSentId": 803}, {"answer": "What I mean is I went to a doctor who said, OK, if \"People Magazine\" and \"Entertainment Tonight\" cover it, I'll comp it.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 810, "question": "ORGAN: What do you mean a trade out?", "qSentId": 809}, {"answer": "I was supposed to be Jennifer Anniston.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "What did you hope would happen to you?", "qSentId": 816}, {"answer": "It's just -- it just doesn't really do anything.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "What went wrong?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "I didn't.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 834, "question": "Did you go to Dr. Robert Maloney?", "qSentId": 833}, {"answer": "I love Twitter.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "Do you like being engaged in Twitter?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "Oh, I love it.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 863, "question": "How do you deal with the fury that you get?", "qSentId": 862}, {"answer": "No, I like that you don't engage.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "Do you like the engagement on Twitter with people?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 888, "question": "You mean, people @KathyGriffin and @PiersMorgan?", "qSentId": 887}, {"answer": "Yes, she's a good one.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 903, "question": "Does she?", "qSentId": 902}, {"answer": "No, you're not big enough.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 905, "question": "Can you get her to Tweet me in the middle of the night?", "qSentId": 904}, {"answer": "Every night.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 945, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 944}, {"answer": "You are done for about two minutes.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 958, "question": "Are we done now?", "qSentId": 957}, {"answer": "I love that you made a deal with a doctor for plastic surgery.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 975, "question": "You mean my botched laser surgery?", "qSentId": 974}, {"answer": "Yeah, of course.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 982, "question": "Did you have to mention the doctor's name in interviews?", "qSentId": 981}, {"answer": "You're still live on air.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1018, "question": "How does this work?", "qSentId": 1017}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1020, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 1019}, {"answer": "Oh, you did not -- I'll throw this mike pack at your --", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1034, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 1033}, {"answer": "I've never counted.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1041, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 1040}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1043, "question": "Like how many guys have I slept with?", "qSentId": 1042}, {"answer": "As many as are truthful.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1045, "question": "How many digits would make you happy?", "qSentId": 1044}, {"answer": "You.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1052, "question": "If you could be trapped on a desert island for the rest of your life, right now, with one of your exes, who would it be?", "qSentId": 1051}, {"answer": "I'm single, but I'm dating.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1064, "question": "Are you single at the moment?", "qSentId": 1063}, {"answer": "Guys that ask me.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1066, "question": "Who are you dating?", "qSentId": 1065}, {"answer": "The ones who I happen to be home when they call.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1068, "question": "Any in particular?", "qSentId": 1067}, {"answer": "Seriously.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1076, "question": "It's a nightmare, right?", "qSentId": 1075}, {"answer": "Well, I'm super-excited when a guy picks up the tab and has a job.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1078, "question": "How do they go?", "qSentId": 1077}, {"answer": "I'm happy for a good lay and a pizza and a smile.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1088, "question": "Are you or not?", "qSentId": 1087}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1092, "question": "Would you like to get married again?", "qSentId": 1091}, {"answer": "Did that.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1094, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 1093}, {"answer": "I have a special needs child.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1100, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 1099}, {"answer": "Well, after this, it's in the crapper because of this.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1107, "question": "How do you see your life panning out?", "qSentId": 1106}, {"answer": "Loved it.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1109, "question": "No, I love to do what -- it was fun when you had that show on CNN, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 1108}, {"answer": "No, I went to the Emmy's last year.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1120, "question": "Now do you go to the Emmy's or are you too high and mighty?", "qSentId": 1119}, {"answer": "I haven't decided yet.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1125, "question": "Who is doing your dress?", "qSentId": 1124}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1134, "question": "Didn't I see you standing outside one of the pre-Emmy parties last time trying to meet people?", "qSentId": 1133}, {"answer": "I'm the greeter at the --", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1137, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 1136}, {"answer": "Yes, it was funny.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1152, "question": "RIFFIN: Did you enjoy it?", "qSentId": 1151}, {"answer": "Because you're going to check your Twitter.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1165, "question": "Why am I now really nervous about the last five minutes?", "qSentId": 1164}, {"answer": "Old pal of mine, absolutely.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1181, "question": "Friend of yours?", "qSentId": 1180}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1183, "question": "Rival?", "qSentId": 1182}, {"answer": "RIFFIN: Suck it.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1189, "question": "If you had to choose a one-liner to be your last line on Earth, what would it be?", "qSentId": 1188}, {"answer": "You can do it tonight.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1201, "question": "Would you like me to help you?", "qSentId": 1200}, {"answer": "I insist.", "docId": "110806pmt", "aSentId": 1203, "question": "Would you like to do the tease to Anderson?", "qSentId": 1202}]